<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- This is a WordPress eXtended RSS file generated by WordPress as an export of your site. -->
<!-- It contains information about your site's posts, pages, comments, categories, and other content. -->
<!-- You may use this file to transfer that content from one site to another. -->
<!-- This file is not intended to serve as a complete backup of your site. -->

<!-- To import this information into a WordPress site follow these steps: -->
<!-- 1. Log in to that site as an administrator. -->
<!-- 2. Go to Tools: Import in the WordPress admin panel. -->
<!-- 3. Install the "WordPress" importer from the list. -->
<!-- 4. Activate & Run Importer. -->
<!-- 5. Upload this file using the form provided on that page. -->
<!-- 6. You will first be asked to map the authors in this export file to users -->
<!--    on the site. For each author, you may choose to map to an -->
<!--    existing user on the site or to create a new user. -->
<!-- 7. WordPress will then import each of the posts, pages, comments, categories, etc. -->
<!--    contained in this file into your site. -->

<!-- generator="WordPress/3.5.1" created="2013-07-16 18:29" -->
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:excerpt="http://wordpress.org/export/1.2/excerpt/"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:wp="http://wordpress.org/export/1.2/"
>

<channel>
	<title>TrustNetMD</title>
	<link>http://trustnetmd.com</link>
	<description>Social Knowledge Applications for Healthcare</description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2013 18:29:05 +0000</pubDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<wp:wxr_version>1.2</wp:wxr_version>
	<wp:base_site_url>http://trustnetmd.com</wp:base_site_url>
	<wp:base_blog_url>http://trustnetmd.com</wp:base_blog_url>

	<wp:author><wp:author_id>1</wp:author_id><wp:author_login>trustadmin</wp:author_login><wp:author_email>sking@trustnetmd.com</wp:author_email><wp:author_display_name><![CDATA[Trust Admin]]></wp:author_display_name><wp:author_first_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:author_first_name><wp:author_last_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:author_last_name></wp:author>
	<wp:author><wp:author_id>2</wp:author_id><wp:author_login>johnmay</wp:author_login><wp:author_email>jmay@trustnetmd.com</wp:author_email><wp:author_display_name><![CDATA[John May]]></wp:author_display_name><wp:author_first_name><![CDATA[John]]></wp:author_first_name><wp:author_last_name><![CDATA[May]]></wp:author_last_name></wp:author>
	<wp:author><wp:author_id>3</wp:author_id><wp:author_login>richard</wp:author_login><wp:author_email>rsingerman@trustnetmd.com</wp:author_email><wp:author_display_name><![CDATA[Richard Singerman]]></wp:author_display_name><wp:author_first_name><![CDATA[Richard]]></wp:author_first_name><wp:author_last_name><![CDATA[Singerman]]></wp:author_last_name></wp:author>


	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=3.5.1</generator>

	<item>
		<title>Home</title>
		<link>http://trustnetmd.com/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2013 11:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>trustadmin</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://iti-partners.com/trustnetmd.com/?page_id=2</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>[metaslider id=424] TrustNetMD combines organizational learning priciples and social media technologies to create "social learning solutuons" that address the challenges of communication, collaboration, coordination and consensus building in healthcare transformation. Focused professional communities are needed to solve complex problems, often caused by <em>cultural misalignment</em>. Our Knowledge Exchange (Kx) platform serves as the communications backbone of what quickly becomes a tightly-knit learning collaborative—no matter whether there are dozens or hundreds of users engaged in the initiative.</p><p>For example,  a culture of safety depends on a culture of teamwork. And effective clinical teams require close communication, collaboration and coordination. However, current efforts to create this culture of teamwork and collaboration are labor intensive and do not scale. TrustNetMD's Knowledge Exchange (Kx) platform leverages the power of social media connecting silos, removing friction, and ultimately releasing value trapped in our healthcare system.  </p><p><img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-455" alt="tablet1" src="http://trustnetmd.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/06/tablet1.png" width="143" height="122" /></p><p>Achieve faster adoption of new programs, building of comprehensive best practices, integration of new technology, building detailed requirements for capital projects, training on new software (say EHRs), identifying new knowledge based thought leaders based on their community contribution, or enabling of grassroots feedback from large groups.</p><p>TrustNetMD’s secure, cloud-based Kx™ applications are as easy to use as Google Search and Gmail. They are accessed by mobile or desktop and need not be part of an organization’s IT infrastructure.</p><p><img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-459" alt="woman-doctor-call-out" src="http://trustnetmd.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/06/woman-doctor-call-out.png" width="646" height="242" /></p><p><i>Kx communities enable communication, collaboration and coordination. Community discussions that take place at a time and place convenient to the participants are much more likely to get thoughtful contributions.</i></p><p class="medium"><a class="button" href="http://trustnetmd.iti-partners.com/?page_id=24">Let's Talk</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>2</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2013-06-05 11:20:12</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2013-06-05 11:20:12</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>sample-page</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>page</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wp_page_template</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[3]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_responsive_layout</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_rawhtml_settings</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0,1,1,0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>About Us</title>
		<link>http://trustnetmd.com/about-us/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2013 17:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>trustadmin</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://trustnetmd.iti-partners.com/?page_id=5</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h5>A passion for healthcare and elegant technology solutions</h5><p><img class=" wp-image-473 alignright" alt="puzzle-chain2" src="http://trustnetmd.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/06/puzzle-chain2-e1370946360294.png" width="144" height="252" />TrustNetMD’s team has telecommunications, healthcare, innovation, and web media experience. </p><p>If you have a need for a virtual content community or<br />process improvement solution in the healthcare field...</p><div class="medium"><a class="button" href="http://trustnetmd.com/?page_id=24">Let's Talk</a></div><div class="medium"> </div><div class="even"><h5><a name="1"></a><img class="wp-image-392 alignleft" alt="John pic" src="http://trustnetmd.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/06/John-pic-273x300.jpg" width="92" height="101" />John May</h5><p>Chief Executive Officer (CEO)<br /><a style="font-size: 0.83em;" href="mailto:jmay@trustnetmd.com" target="_blank">jmay@TrustNetMD.com</a></p><p> John May is CEO of TrustNetMD, a company that helps customers with the challenge of integrating networking technology, new applications, and new devices into the business of healthcare. He serves on the Board of Trustees and Executive Committee of Sibley Memorial/Johns Hopkins Hospital in Washington, D.C.</p><p>His passion is to bring problem solvers, individuals as well as company-wide, to focus on the delivery of healthcare. Integrated and coordinated care using technology will result in a value chain that will transform healthcare to its fullest potential.</p><p>He understands the innovation process needed to start a business transformation recently experienced by so many industries. He spent 30 years in telecommunications where he found the ability to communicate effectively was central to the innovation process. He is using his understanding of networks, applications like CRM, BI, social media, and smart devices to obtain orders of magnitude increases in productivity, all of which has enabled so much modernization in these other industries.</p><p>He has a master’s degree in Computer Science from Johns Hopkins University (Applied Physics Lab), an MBA (Finance - Honors) from American University, and a BS in Mathematics from Marietta College. He received a commission in the Air Force and joined the Strategic Air Command (SAC). Member of Mindshare</p></div><div class="odd"><h5><img alt="" src="http://trustnetmd.com/wp-content/uploads/images/headshot-richard2.jpg" width="100" height="125" align="left" /><a name="15"></a>Richard Singerman, Ph.D.</h5><p>Chief Innovation Officer (CIO)<br /><a style="font-size: 0.83em;" href="mailto:rsingerman@trustnetmd.com" target="_blank">rsingerman@trustnetmd.com</a></p><p>Richard Singerman had been an Associate Partner in IBM's Healthcare Transformation &amp; Analytics practice where he was responsible for developing and implementing initiatives to support health system transformation. Before that he served in the Office of the National Coordinator for Health Information Technology, US Department of Health and Human Services. Richard's public service was preceded by his role as Director of Innovation and Knowledge Sharing for Ascension Health, the nation's largest nonprofit health care system. He is a member of the Advisory Board for BNA’s Health IT &amp; Law Industry Report and the author of numerous articles and reports concerning health care trends, knowledge sharing, diagnostic imaging, and additional innovations necessary to elevating quality and performance. He holds a Ph.D. in Physics from Cornell University, a Masters in Applied Mathematics from Cambridge University, and a BS in Physics from the Massachusetts Institute of Technology.</p></div><div class="even"><h5><img alt="" src="http://www.trustnetmd.com/wp-content/uploads/images/headshot-rick_stuntz_headshot.jpg" width="136" align="left" /><a name="22"></a>Richard Stuntz</h5><p>Chief Operating Officer (COO)<br /><a href="mailto:rstuntz@trustnetmd.com" target="_blank">rstuntz@trustnetmd.com</a></p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>Rick Stuntz has experience with management and operation of mission-critical systems in a secure hosted environment. Most recently Rick was responsible for the deployment and operation of hosted systems for State and Local Governments accessible by over 30 million Americans, including Florida and California. In his 30 year career working with Genuity, GTE and BBN, he has focused on the challenges of scale: how to design and operate systems able to meet rapidly escalating customer requirements. Rick has a degree from Duke University and attended MIT Sloan School’s Executive Education Program.</p></div><div class="odd"><h5><img alt="" src="http://www.trustnetmd.com/wp-content/uploads/images/headshot-lorraine.gif" width="100" height="125" align="left" /><a name="5"></a>Lorraine Fordham</h5><p>Vice President, Client Services<br /><a style="font-size: 0.83em;" href="mailto:lfordham@trustnetmd.com" target="_blank">lfordham@TrustNetMD.com</a></p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>Prior to joining TrustNetMD in 2008, Lorraine Fordham was CIO of Sibley Memorial Hospital in Washington, D.C. As CIO of this 328-bed community hospital, she had direct, hands-on responsibility for overall IT management; all software and hardware evaluation, acquisition and implementation; IT strategy and E-business strategies; and HIPAA and JCAHO compliance. She chaired the 25-member Clinical Systems Advisory Committee composed of physicians, nurses and department heads, and was co-chair of the 22-member IT Steering Committee made up of senior executives and medical staff leaders. She was instrumental in advancing the use of technology to improve business processes and hospital operations.</p><p>Lorraine holds a BS in Technology and Business Management from the University of Maryland and is a Certified Professional in Healthcare Information and Management Systems. She is a member of the American College of Healthcare Executives, HIMSS, and the College of Health Information Management Executives.</p></div><div class="even"><h5><img alt="" src="http://www.trustnetmd.com/wp-content/uploads/images/headshot-SK-pic125x100.jpg" width="100" height="125" align="left" /><a name="sk"></a>Steven King</h5><p>Software Designer and Social Media Architect<br /><a style="font-size: 0.83em;" href="mailto:sking@trustnetmd.com" target="_blank">sking@TrustNetMD.com</a></p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>Steven King is a veteran technologist and software designer with 20 years of hands-on experience in the areas of IT, application development, social media, knowledge community design and industry analysis. He has consulted for Cisco, Intel, HP, Dell, Microsoft, Motorola, IBM, Microsoft, DoD and McGraw-Hill.</p><p>Steve's UI/UX design and product management expertise has been applied to a wide range of high velocity start-up ventures and large enterprise software projects, including  social networking sites, professional knowledge sharing communities, transaction workflows,  CRM,  supply chain, mobile commerce and various Web 2.0 applications.</p></div><div class="odd"><h5><a name="6"></a><a style="font-size: 13px; font-weight: normal;" href="http://trustnetmd.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/06/KAWWASS-IMAGE-1-4x5-color-copy.jpeg"><img class="wp-image-383 alignleft" style="margin-right: 3px;" alt="KAWWASS IMAGE-1-4x5-color copy" src="http://trustnetmd.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/06/KAWWASS-IMAGE-1-4x5-color-copy-238x300.jpeg" width="86" height="108" /></a>Bassam A. Kawwass, MHA, FACHE</h5><p>Advisor<br /><a href="mailto:bkawwass@cval.org">bkawwass@cval.org</a></p><p>  </p><p>Bassam Kawwass is an Advisor to TrustNetMD following an extensive career overseeing the operational issues of physician-hospital alignment, practice management, and medical center performance improvement. He has served as CEO of a 350-bed hospital and directed ambulatory services at a 420-bed teaching hospital, as well as served in increasingly responsible positions at the University of Maryland Medical Center, Hariri Medical Center, Saudi Hospital Management Company, Hospital Supply International, First Hospital Corporation, Sentara Health System, and others leading healthcare organizations. Previously he served two terms as president of the Virginia chapter of the American College of Healthcare Executives where he received both the ACHE’s Leadership Award and its Distinguished Service Award (2011). Mr. Kawwass holds an MHA from the Medical College of Virginia, gained health information management training at St. Louis University, and received a BA in Business Administration from the American University of Beirut. He is a Registered Health Information Administrator (RHIA) and a Board Certified Fellow Healthcare Executive (FACHE).</p></div><div class="even"><h5><a name="7"></a>Ron Dionne, MD</h5><p>Advisor<br /><a style="font-size: 0.83em;" href="mailto:rdionne@trustnetmd.com" target="_blank">rdionne@TrustNetMD.com</a></p><p>Ron Dionne is a board-certified pediatrician and an experienced medical software designer. From 2000-2008, he was at Allscripts where he was the product manager for 12 individual modules of the company's electronic health record, TouchWorks, as well as the clinical lead for its latest design and for patient safety. Previously, he was medical director at Medifor, a privately held patient education software company. He has an MD from the University of Medicine and Dentistry of New Jersey and a BA with a major in Biology from Boston University. Ron has an abiding interest in patient education, physician decision support, EHR design and ihealth solutions.</p></div><div class="odd"><h5><img alt="" src="http://www.trustnetmd.com/wp-content/uploads/images/headshot-pat.gif" width="100" height="125" align="left" /><a name="2"></a>D. P. Alagia III, MD</h5><p>Advisor<br /><a style="font-size: 0.83em;" href="mailto:palagia@TrustNetMD.com" target="_blank">palagia@TrustNetMD.com</a></p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>Pat Alagia is a physician executive who is a board-certified obstetrician and gynecologist with extensive experience in building physician networks in the world of academics, medical society politics, private clinical practice, and private equity-based physician services. Prior to joining TrustNetMD, Pat was president of Safe Sedation Management, a private equity-backed  anesthesia service provider for ambulatory surgical centers and GI endoscopy centers.  His academic background includes serving as an associate clinical professor and founding program director of Minimally Invasive Gynecologic Surgery (MIGS) at The George Washington University Hospital, and as an adjunct clinical professor at Georgetown University Hospital. Concurrent with his work in minimally invasive surgery, Pat advised ETHICON Women’s Health and Urology, a Johnson &amp; Johnson company, and Immersion Medical where he was a SME for product development and products in use. From 1988-2005, he was founder and chairman of Women’s Health Corp., a clinical group practice focused on the care of women. From 2001-2004, Pat was finance committee co-chairman of the National Capital Reciprocal Insurance Company, before its sale to ProAssurance (PRA).</p><p>Pat holds an MBA in Finance from Johns Hopkins University. His MD and BS degrees are from Georgetown University. He is a Fellow of both the American College of Surgeons and the American College of Obstetricians and Gynecologists. He repeatedly has been selected as among “Washington’s Best Doctors,” and has led the Medical Society of the District of Columbia as its president.</p></div><div class="even"><h5><a name="8"></a></h5></div><div class="odd"><h5><a name="10"></a>Michael Peterson</h5><p>Advisor<br /><a style="font-size: 0.83em;" href="mailto:mpeterson@trustnetmd.com" target="_blank">mpeterson@TrustNetMD.com</a></p><p>Michael Peterson is a technology strategist with more than 25 years of experience in management, selection, and system/product design and development in business and government. Mike was a Linguateq co-founder, and he holds patents related to data mediation and manipulation.</p><p>Mike's recent interests concern mashups and content management, mobile IM infrastructure and applications, DNS technologies, IP-based products, and telecommunications next-gen OSS services. He frequently runs software development projects with 200+ developers worldwide, and defines and delivers prototypes/POC. He is also a regular speaker at industry events, such as Oracle World, a participant in the Oracle National SOA Leadership Council, and a media presence in such forums as Ziff Davis SOA Web-Broadcasts. He is a founder of the Washington SOA Users Group, and is called on in the IT sector to help define emerging standards (TAC).</p></div><div class="even"><h5><a name="11"></a>Rick Abbott</h5><p>Advisor<br /><a style="font-size: 0.83em;" href="mailto:rabbott@trustnetmd.com" target="_blank">rabbott@TrustNetMD.com</a></p><p><em id="__mceDel"> Rick Abbott has more than 20 years of experience in information technology consulting. He brings deep telecom industry experience, focused on large-scale data integration and business intelligence projects, with responsibility for case development and strategic alignment, requirements, technical architecture and design. He has had P&amp;L responsibility for a $10M consulting practice, and has more than 15 years of experience as a program and project manager for multimillion-dollar IT implementation engagements. Until 2000, he was an associate partner at Deloitte Consulting, and previously a senior consultant at Andersen Consulting. He holds a BS in Computer Science from Purdue University.</em></p></div>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>5</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2013-06-05 17:09:24</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2013-06-05 17:09:24</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>about-us</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>1</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>page</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wp_page_template</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_responsive_layout</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_rawhtml_settings</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1,1,1,1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[225]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>The Challenge</title>
		<link>http://trustnetmd.com/the-challenge/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2013 19:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>trustadmin</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://trustnetmd.iti-partners.com/?page_id=13</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Recent CMS Administrator Dr. Donald Berwick states that “tempo” is his key priority for improving the quality, safety, and cost of America’s healthcare. Knowledge, skills, and standards exist—but hospitals move too slowly in putting these strengths to work.</p><p><a href="http://trustnetmd.iti-partners.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/06/callout_problem.png"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-50" alt="callout_problem" src="http://trustnetmd.iti-partners.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/06/callout_problem.png" width="646" height="242" /></a></p><p>Consider how difficult it is to coordinate clinical and operational improvement initiatives that affect multiple service lines; especially in the new ACA environment.  ACO models now need to focus on the efficiency of care delivery as intently as they used to focus on clinical care.</p><p>Unfortunately it is all the harder to overcome traditional, outdated ways of doing things especially given the increased work load of the problem solving community.  They often are in different environmental silos which reduces consensus and ultimate adoption.  Email boxes overflow. time is burned up in meetings. Group conference calls are difficult to attend. Webinars and blogs induce too little interaction. New ideas and even new potential leaders cannot penetrate through the clutter.</p><blockquote><p><i>We founded TrustNetMD because we believe this is our chance to tap into the knowledge and experience of our communities, who are dealing with issues at the grassroots level.  Listen to the knowledge and experience of those who have hands on experience day in and day out. Let communication must go both ways.</i></p></blockquote><p>TrustNetMD specializes in knowledge exchanges that manage communities and their interaction. We build communities; find participants and facilitators, often-recognized thought leaders; leaders to lead community interaction, so you can strategize, understand your likelihood and quality of success, what you can do to improve success, and what you need to do to navigate roadblocks to your success. </p><p>[raw]</p><p>If you have a need for a virtual content community or<br /> process improvement solution in the healthcare field...</p><div class="medium"><a class="button" href="http://trustnetmd.com/?page_id=24">Let's Talk</a></div><div class="medium">[/raw]</div>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>13</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2013-06-05 19:01:45</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2013-06-05 19:01:45</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>the-challenge</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>2</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>page</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[2]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wp_page_template</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_responsive_layout</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_rawhtml_settings</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1,0,1,0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Our Approach</title>
		<link>http://trustnetmd.com/our-approach/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2013 19:19:55 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>trustadmin</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://trustnetmd.iti-partners.com/?page_id=16</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Our approach is to build an <strong>empowered community</strong>.  Let users navigate with their browsers to pose questions, add images and hyperlinks, upload documents and test answers, offer insights easily. Supply added resources through a  Web 2.0 ontological as well as traditional APIs. Get knowledge organized automatically as the community ranks its content and prioritizes its findings.  By doing so we harness the power of conversations taking place in a community. In conjunction with typical hard informational assets such as databases, reports, articles, and research publications, capturing the informal dialog of a professional community maximizes a community’s brain trust. Combining such data with research accelerates the adoption of best practices essential to solving complex problems in the healthcare industry. </p><blockquote><p><img class="wp-image-394  alignleft" alt="Componets" src="http://trustnetmd.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/06/Componets.png" width="268" height="214" /></p><h4>An empowered community provides the leverage to get more done</h4><p>Incorporating grass roots dialog into an information strategy empowers the community itself to convey quality healthcare delivery solutions quickly and cost effectively. Proprietary design methods allow us to analyze this social fabric of a community: How consensus was reached; who was involved; what resources did they use; what impact and implications can be derived? This process is particularly important given the sheer number of interested parties that need to be aligned. <span style="color: #800000;"><em>Email, conference calls, and face-to-face meetings are inadequate to meet such complexity.</em></span></p></blockquote><h4>Disruptive Innovation – Foundational factors include leveraging knowledge wherever it is found</h4><ul><li><i>Catalyze community innovation from the inside</i><i> - </i>that is where the knowledge is.</li><li><i>Use methods that are effective and scalable</i><i> - </i>be able to support thousands of members and millions of discussions.  Fewer committee meetings, seminars, reply-all emails.</li><li><i>Utilize all eyes on the groun</i><i>d - </i>no restrictions, geographic or hierarchical, means all members of a community are able, and encouraged, to contribute.</li><li><i>Permit the community, not an outsider, to set the bar</i>  -  seed a culture of innovation by creating an environment that rewards those who are willing to contribute;  an <i>“it’s your house”</i> mentality to encourage broad conversation that leads to improvement.</li><li><i>Ease of use</i> – Our Kx<sup>TM</sup> is easier to use than email.  It is easy to integrate multiple forms of media (data, text, video, articles) in support of a user’s position and can be accessed by all browser connectable devices.</li><li><i>Ongoing learning - </i>extends<i> </i>the ability for a community to maintain  a "learning collaborative base camp."</li></ul><p>Our exchange serves as the communications backbone of what quickly becomes a tightly-knit learning collaborative—no matter whether there are dozens or hundreds of users engaged in the initiative.</p><p>[raw]If you have a need for a virtual content community or<br /> process improvement solution in the healthcare field...</p><div class="medium"><a class="button" href="http://trustnetmd.com/?page_id=24">Let's Talk</a></div><div class="medium">[/raw]</div>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>16</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2013-06-05 19:19:55</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2013-06-05 19:19:55</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>our-approach</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>3</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>page</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[2]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wp_page_template</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_responsive_layout</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_rawhtml_settings</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1,1,1,1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>The Benefits</title>
		<link>http://trustnetmd.com/the-benefits/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2013 19:22:33 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>trustadmin</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://trustnetmd.iti-partners.com/?page_id=22</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h4><b>Empowered Communities</b></h4><p><img class=" wp-image-480 alignright" alt="benefits2" src="http://trustnetmd.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/06/benefits2.png" width="237" height="210" />Effective teams are defined by close communication and collaboration; that is the very definition of “teamwork”.  But recurring meetings and mass emails overwhelm inboxes and schedules. The answer to effectiveness is social media/knowledge exchanges.  This avenue enables efficient communications and collaboration because they are online, available at any time and place. Community meetings/discussions are convenient for the participants and thus are much more likely to get useful, thoughtful contributions that move the team forward.  </p><h4><strong>Benefits - Community interactions providing <br class="none" />insights that lead to: </strong></h4><ul><li>Faster adoption of new products and programs because roadblocks have been addressed; consensus reached</li><li>Building of comprehensive best practices</li><li>Building requirements for new projects and best practices, especially around new technology </li><li>Developing effective messages for new product rollout</li><li>Identifying of thought leaders based on their community contribution </li></ul><blockquote><p><b>Why this is important...<br /></b>To understand the likelihood and quality of your success; to maximize your success; to navigate roadblocks to your success</p></blockquote><h4><strong>Metrics- The Effectiveness of Your Community: </strong></h4><p>Are your participants listening?</p><ul><li>Do they understand?</li><li>Are they responding? </li><li>Do they check back?</li><li>Are they committed?</li><li>Is there consensus?</li><li>How broad is the community reach...</li><li>Does it foster grassroots feedback?</li></ul><p>[raw]If you have a need for a virtual content community or<br /><em id="__mceDel">process improvement solution in the healthcare field...</em></p><div class="medium"><a class="button" href="http://trustnetmd.com/?page_id=24">Let's Talk</a></div><div class="medium">[/raw]</div>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>22</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2013-06-05 19:22:33</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2013-06-05 19:22:33</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>the-benefits</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>4</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>page</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wp_page_template</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_responsive_layout</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_rawhtml_settings</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0,1,1,1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Contact Us</title>
		<link>http://trustnetmd.com/contact-us/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2013 19:23:01 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>trustadmin</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://trustnetmd.iti-partners.com/?page_id=24</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div style="margin-top: 11px; background-color: #eaf1f8; padding: 10px; border: 1px solid #ddd; border-radius: 4px;"><h3><strong>Contact us:</strong></h3><p>TrustNetMD<br /> 1701 Pennsylvania Avenue, NW<br /> Suite 300<br /> Washington, D.C. 20006<br /> Phone: 703.624.2719</p></div><div style="background-color: #eaf1f8; padding: 10px; margin: 3px 0 10px 0; border: 1px solid #ddd; border-radius: 4px;"><strong>John May</strong><br /> CEO<br /> jmay@TrustNetMD.com</div><p>[raw]</p><script type="text/javascript" src="http://form.jotformpro.com/jsform/31557397670969"></script><p>[/raw]</p>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>24</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2013-06-05 19:23:01</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2013-06-05 19:23:01</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>contact-us</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>9</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>page</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wp_page_template</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_responsive_layout</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_rawhtml_settings</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1,1,1,1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Think: Knowledge Exchange</title>
		<link>http://trustnetmd.com/the-benefits/think-knowledge-exchange/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 00:06:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>trustadmin</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://trustnetmd.iti-partners.com/?page_id=130</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://trustnetmd.iti-partners.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/06/think-ke.png" target="_blank"><img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-131" alt="think-ke" src="http://trustnetmd.iti-partners.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/06/think-ke.png" width="1170" height="776" /></a>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>130</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2013-06-06 00:06:06</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2013-06-06 00:06:06</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>think-knowledge-exchange</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>22</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>2</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>page</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wp_page_template</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[full-width-page.php]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_responsive_layout</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Knowledge Exchange Primer </title>
		<link>http://trustnetmd.com/the-benefits/knowledge-exchange-primer/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 00:13:15 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>trustadmin</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://trustnetmd.iti-partners.com/?page_id=136</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Self-organizing, self-policing platforms for </strong><strong>social-knowledge applications</strong></p><p>Knowledge Exchanges should be used when knowledge needs to be moved across a network of dispersed individuals quickly, and when long email strings containing various disconnected attachments become unworkable. This break point occurs typically when the group grows beyond about 20 members but can be as low as 6 if highly collaborative knowledge sharing and problem solving is needed by people who are not in the same location all the time. [metaslider id=339]</p><p><strong>Ease of Use:</strong> Questions are submitted to the community and answers to those questions are in the center column. Voting on both questions and answers can be seen on the left. Tagging, the method used for navigating the site, is to be seen on the right. Contents, both questions and answers, can have embedded documents, hyperlinks to supporting material such as research papers, PDFs, images, video, MP3 audio recordings, etc.</p><p><strong>Reputation:</strong> Unlike traditional online discussion forums, blogs, wikis and other social media, the Knowledge Exchange is based on elegant new software algorithms that automatically protect it from undesirable user behaviors, while it organizes and refines content. Users initially have limited rights on the system but if they behave well they are increasingly given reputation points that enable additional editorial privileges. This avoids the traditional pitfalls of online discussion forums and blog comment threads that are plagued with spam, flaming, and irrelevant or offensive content.</p><p><strong>Self-Refinement:</strong> Users can easily vote Knowledge Exchange content up or down, based on the degree to which each user finds particular questions and answers to be relevant, helpful, and authoritative. User tagging makes content easy to query and retrieve. These and related self-refining and self-organizing knowledge capabilities ensure that the most useful and relevant content floats to the top of the site. Since trusted end users can edit, order, tag and refine content, the Knowledge Exchange creates a sort of canonical “living” knowledge base that is not attainable via conventional social media or Knowledge Management (KM) systems.</p><p><strong>The Power of Tagging:</strong> A tag is the equivalent of a subject and is a powerful attribute of our Knowledge Exchange. Tags can be associated with particular organizational functions (e.g. Finance) so that the Finance group, for example, can be alerted via email when a question is added with the Finance tag. Members (students and faculty) are alerted based on tags that interest them. Members are alerted if they post a question and that question gets answered.</p><p><strong> </strong></p><p>&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>136</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2013-06-06 00:13:15</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2013-06-06 00:13:15</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>knowledge-exchange-primer</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>22</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>1</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>page</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wp_page_template</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_responsive_layout</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_rawhtml_settings</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1,0,1,0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>The Benefits</title>
		<link>http://trustnetmd.com/the-benefits/httptrustnetmd-iti-partners-comcontact-us/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 00:20:56 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>trustadmin</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://trustnetmd.iti-partners.com/?page_id=142</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>[raw]</p><script type="text/javascript">// <![CDATA[
window.location.replace("http://trustnetmd.com/the-benefits/");
// ]]]]><![CDATA[></script><p>[/raw]</p>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>142</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2013-06-06 00:20:56</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2013-06-06 00:20:56</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>httptrustnetmd-iti-partners-comcontact-us</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>22</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>page</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wp_page_template</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_responsive_layout</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_rawhtml_settings</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1,1,1,1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>
